const quizQuestions = [
    {
      question: "who was the shortest nba player ever?",
  
      answers: ["Steve Nash", "Muggsy Bogues", "Yao Ming", "Nate Robinson"],
  
      correct: "Muggsy Bogues"
    },
  
      {
      question: "who was the tallest nba player ever?",
  
      answers: ["Manute Bol", "Shawn Bradley", "Yao Ming", "Dikembe Mutombo"],
  
      correct: "Manute Bol"
    },
  
      {
      question: "who is the youngest player to ever play in the nba?",
  
      answers: ["Lebron James", "Kobe Bryant", "Andrew Bynum", "Vince Carter"],
  
      correct: "Andrew Bynum"
    },
  
       {
      question: "who scored the most points in an nba game?",
  
      answers: ["Kobe Bryant", "Wilt Chamberlain", "Magic Johnson", "MIcheal Jordan"],
  
      correct: "Wilt Chamberlain"
     },
    
     {
     question: "How many rings does Bill Russel have?",
  
      answers: [6, 5, 8, 11],
  
      correct: 11
     },
     {
     question: "Most minutes played in nba history by who?",
     
     answers: ["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "Karl Malone", "Dirk Nowitzki", "Kevin Garnett"],
     
     correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
    },
    {
     question: "who has the most 3 pointers made in nba history",
     
     answers: ["Stephen Curry", "Reggie Miller", "Ray Allen" , "Jason Terry" ],
     
     correct: "Ray Allen"
    },
    {
    question: "Which player was NOT drafted out of high school?",
        
    answers: ['Kobe Bryant', 'Kevin Garnett', 'LeBron James' , 'Shaquille O\'neal' ],
        
    correct: 'Shaquille O\'neal'
    },
    {
        question: "'Which state has the most NBA teams?'",
            
        answers: ["New York", "California", "Texas" , "Florida" ],
            
        correct: "California"
    },
    {
        question: "Who has the highest points per game in NBA playoff history?",
            
        answers: ["Jerry West", "Allen Iverson", "Lebron James" , "Michael Jordan" ],
            
        correct: "Michael Jordan"
    },
    {
        question: "what player has the most nba playoff wins",
            
        answers: ["Tim Duncan", "Michael Jordan", "Derek Fisher" , "Lebron James" ],
            
        correct: "Derek Fisher"
    }           
  ];